A Guide to the Studies of the Virginia Division of Legislative Services, 1978-2000.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Legislative Services, Virginia Division of, Studies
1978-2000.
The Library of Virginia
39745, 40083, 40914, 42271, 42785, 43390
Virginia. Division of Legislative Services.
188 cu. ft.
Biographical/Historical Information
On March 21, 1914 the Legislative Reference Bureau was created within the Office of the Attorney General by an act of the General Assembly. Its primary purpose was to draft legislation for the governor and members of the General Assembly, collect materials related to proposed legislation, maintain files of all legislative documents, and to analyze the legal effects and other aspects of proposed legislation. The agency was to be run by a director appointed by the Governor. On March 24, 1930 the General Assembly changed the name to the Divison of Statutory Research and Drafting and the Division was moved from the Office of the Attorney General to the legislative branch of state government. The director of the Division was required to periodically review the statutory law of the Commonwealth and to suggest changes to the governor. In addition to drafting legislation, the agency was also charged with legal support services for the General Assembly.
The Division of Statutory Research and Drafting was reorganized into the Division of Legislative Services on March 15, 1973. Its director is appointed by the General Assembly and serves at the pleasure of committees on rules of the Senate and House of Delegates. By 1975 the Legislative Process Commission concluded that the General Assembly needed greater research capabilities. That same year, the Division was given the responsibility of providing both legal and research staff support to all standing committees of both houses of the General Assembly. In 1989, under new leadership, the Division was organized into operational sections, currently Business and Jurisprudence; Finance and Government; and Rules, Education, Elections and Special Projects. The Division's major responsibilities include conducting legal and general research, drafting legislation, providing staff support to all standing committees and legislative study committees, subcommittees and commissions, evaluating the constitutionality and legal effects of legislation, and performing various other member services. The mission of the Division of Legislative Services is to assist legislators in fulfilling their duties and obligations as members of the General Assembly.
Scope and Content
These General Assembly authorized staff studies document the research activities used to develop and write drafts and final reports on various topics. The records substantiate study findings, conclusions, recommendations and methodology. May include correspondence, working papers, reference material, minutes, meeting agendas, and notes, presentations, research/background material, legislative draft proposals, clippings/articles, presentations, audiotapes, videotapes, study plans and objectives, public hearing comments/transcripts, and reports.
Arranged by study.
Acquisition Information
Accession 39745 was transferred by the Virginia Division of Legislative Services, July 12, 2002.
Contents List
- Studies (Accession 39745), 1978-1995., Extent: 12 cubic feet (12 boxes)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - HJR 339, 1985. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Human Rights Study Commission, 1985-1987. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights Study Commission, 1985-1987. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights Study Commission, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Correspondence, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Materials, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Meetings, 1985. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Meetings (HJR 33), 1986. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Reference materials, 1985. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Reference materials, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Reference materials, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Report draft, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Report draft (Strother), 1987. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Virginia Advisory Committee to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, 1985 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Virginia Advisory Committee to the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, 1985 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Cities, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Counties, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Fair Employment and Housing, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Employment Trends and Discrimination, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - HJR 339 / SJR 140 Minutes, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Reports, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Towns, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Alaska, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Arizona, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Idaho, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Florida, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Illinois, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Indiana, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Maine, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Michigan, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Missouri, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Nebraska, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - New Jersey, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - New York, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - North Dakota, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Oklahoma, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Oregon, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Tennessee, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Texas, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Utah, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Vermont, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Washington, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - West Virginia, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Human Rights Study Commission - Wisconsin, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Special Working Group on the Care Which Should Be Given by Pet Shops, Kennels, and Breeders of Dogs, Cats and Other Household Pets (SJR 177) - Report, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Special Working Group on the Care Which Should Be Given by Pet Shops, Kennels, and Breeders of Dogs, Cats and Other Household Pets (SJR 177), 1992. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Special Joint Subcommittee Studying the Preservation of Trees, 1988. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying the Relationship between the State and Indian Tribes (HJR 97), 1982. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Water Supply and Wastewater Treatment, 1988. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Recruitment and Retention Incentives for the National Guard, 1983. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Industrial Development and Bond Act Study Commission (HJR 11) - Minutes, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - State and Federal Laws on Privacy, Confidentiality, and Mandatory Disclosure of Information Held or Used by Government Agencies (HJR 66) (folder 1 of 3), 1996. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - State and Federal Laws on Privacy, Confidentiality, and Mandatory Disclosure of Information Held or Used by Government Agencies (HJR 66) (folder 2 of 3), 1996. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - State and Federal Laws on Privacy, Confidentiality, and Mandatory Disclosure of Information Held or Used by Government Agencies (HJR 66) (folder 3 of 3), 1996. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Privacy Laws, 1994. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Privacy Laws - Epilogue, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Privacy Laws - Final Report, 1996. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Privacy Laws - Glass Walls, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Privacy Laws - Meetings, 1994. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Privacy Laws - Reference materials (folder 1 of 2), 1989-1994. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Privacy Laws - Refernce materials (folder 2 of 2), 1989-1994. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Privacy Laws - Survey responses (folder 1 of 4), 1994. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Privacy Laws - Survey responses (folder 2 of 4), 1994. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Privacy Laws - Survey responses (folder 3 of 4), 1994. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Privacy Laws - Survey responses (folder 4 of 4), 1994. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532), 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance, 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance, 1993-1995. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance, 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance, 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Impletmentation Manual, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Implementing National Voter Registration Act of 1993, 1994. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance - Legal Opinions, 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance - Legal Opinions, 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance - Legal Opinions, 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance - Other States, 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532) - Voter Assistance Survey, 1991-1992. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532/ HJR 30 / HD 30), 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532/ HJR 30 / HD 30), 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532), 1993-1996. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532), 1993-1996. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 30), 1994. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Voter Registration Act (HJR 532), 1994-1995. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Family Friendly Work Policy (SJR 279 / HJR 581), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Family Friendly Work Policy (SJR 279 / HJR 581), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Planning Committee High Performance Workforce, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Annexation Laws (HJR 25) - City Reports, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Annexation Laws (HJR 25) - Minutes, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Annexation Laws (HJR 25), 1983. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Annexation Laws (HJR 25) (HJR 599, 1979), 1983. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Annexation Laws (HJR 25), 1983. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood (HJR 34), 1978-1984. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Statehood (HJR 34), 1978-1984. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Wheeling Power (HJR 334), 1989. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Wheeling Power (HJR 334), 1989. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Creative Solutions for Funding the Arts (HJR 174) - Materials and approval letters, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Creative Solutions for Funding the Arts (HJR 174) - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Creative Solutions for Funding the Arts (HJR 174) - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Creative Solutions for Funding the Arts (HJR 174) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Creative Solutions for Funding the Arts (HJR 174) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Creative Solutions for Funding the Arts (HJR 174) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Creative Solutions for Funding the Arts (HJR 174) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Availability of Dental Hygienists (HJR 81), 1996. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Availability of Dental Hygienists (HJR 81), 1996. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Geographic Information Authority (VGIN)(HJR 640), 1995. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Geographic Information Authority (VGIN) (HJR 640), 1995. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Geographic Information Authority (VGIN) (HJR 640), 1995. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Development of Legislation (HJR 13), 1992. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Issues Regarding Informed Consent to Medical Procedures and Treatment (SJR 313), 1995. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Confidentiality Between Patient and Mental Health Providers (HJR 559), 1995. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Correspondence, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Workbook, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Meetings, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - News clippings, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Electronic filing and access, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Session limits, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Articles, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Cases, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Finance Reform (HJR 63) - Cases, 1996. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Transferable Development Rights, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Materials on Local Government (HJR 6 / HJR 286), 1983. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Zoning, 1981. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Zoning, 1982. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Zoning, 1980. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Correspondence (SJR 131), 1986. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - City-County relationships (HJR 163), 1986. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - City-County relationships, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Trash Flow Study, 1984. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - HJR 6, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Structures and Relationshipgs, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Correspondence, 1987. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Reports (HJR 163), 1986. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Meetings (HJR 163), 1986. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Materials (HJR 163), 1986. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Correspondence (HJR 163), 1987. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Reports (HJR 163), 1987. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Meetings (HJR 163), 1987. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Zoning (HJR 125), 1988. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Zoning Correspondence, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - HJR 286, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Cassettes, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Reports, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Correspondence, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Materials, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Drafts, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Materials, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Materials, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Meetings and minutes, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Meetings and minutes (HJR 286), 1989. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Meetings and minutes, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Drafts/Meetings (HJR 298), 1989. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Drafts, 1989. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - Reference Materials, 1980-1987. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - HJR 6 / HJR 286 - Transferable Development Rights, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Commission on Local Government / Grayson Commission - HJR 6 / HJR 286 - Transferable Development Rights, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act, 1986. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act - AG materials, 1986. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act - AG materials, 1986. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act - Drafts (1 and 2), 1987. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act - Drafts (3 and 4), 1987. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act - SJR 68, 1986. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act - Special Session, 1987. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Conflict of Interest Act - Special Session, 1987. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Desirability and Feasibility of Conducting Elections on Saturday and Sunday, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Desirability and Feasibility of Conducting Elections on Saturday and Sunday - Reference material, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Procedures for Identifying Legislation for Imposing Mandates on Local Government (HJR 615), 1995. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Procedures for Identifying Legislation for Imposing Mandates on Local Government (HJR 615) - Reference materials, 1995. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Procedures for Identifying Legislation for Imposing Mandates on Local Government (HJR 615) - Reference materials, 1995. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Background, 1992-1994. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Background, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Background, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Backgroud, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Comments, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Common Cause Reports, 1990-1992. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Computers, 1994. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Draft Subcommittee Report, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Ethics Study, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Executive Orders, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Federal Codes, 1990-1992. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Final Report, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Handouts, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Handouts, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Handouts, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Handouts, 1994. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Information articles, 1987-1991. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Initials background articles, 1990-1992. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Lobbying, 1994. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Lobbying, 1994. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Lobbying, 1994. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Media articles on Ethics, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Memorandums, 1992-1993. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Minutes, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Miscelaneous, 1993-1994. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Miscellaneous, 1994. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Opinions for Reform, 1992. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Other states, undated. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Other states, undated. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Joint Study Commission Studying the Governor's Commission Report on Campaign Finance Reform, Lobbying and Ethics - Other states, undated. (Box 12, Folder 9)